♪ MaryAnn and Wanda were
the best of friends ♪
♪ All through their high school days ♪
♪ Both members of the 4H
Club, both active in the FFA ♪
♪ After graduation, MaryAnn went out ♪
♪ looking for a bright new world ♪
♪ Wanda looked all around this town ♪
♪ And all she found was Earl ♪
♪ Well it wasn't two weeks
after she got married ♪
♪ That Wanda started gettin' abused ♪
♪ She put on dark glasses
and long sleeve blouses ♪
♪ And makeup to cover her bruise ♪
♪ Well she finally got the
nerve to file for divorce ♪
♪ She let the law take it from there ♪
♪ But Earl walked right through
that restraining order ♪
♪ And put 'er in intensive care ♪
♪ Right away MaryAnn
flew in from Atlanta ♪
♪ On a red eye midnight flight ♪
♪ She held Wanda's hand and
they worked out a plan ♪
♪ And it didn't take 'em long to decide ♪
♪ That Earl had to die ♪
♪ Na na na na na ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Earl ♪
♪ Those black eyed peas ♪
♪ Na na na na na na ♪
♪ They tasted alright to me ♪
♪ Earl ♪
♪ You feelin' weak? ♪
♪ Na na na na na ♪
♪ Why don't you lay down and sleep ♪
♪ Earl ♪
♪ Ain't it dark ♪
♪ Na na na na na ♪
♪ Wrapped up in that tarp? ♪
♪ Earl ♪
♪ Cops came by to bring Earl in ♪
♪ They searched the house high and low ♪
♪ Then they tipped their hats
and said thank you ladies ♪
♪ If you hear from him let us know ♪
♪ Well the weeks went by and
Spring turned to Summer ♪
♪ And Summer faded into Fall ♪
♪ And it turns out he
was a missing person ♪
♪ Who nobody missed at all ♪
♪ So the girls bought some land ♪
♪ At a roadside stand ♪
♪ Out on highway 109 ♪
♪ They sell Tennessee
ham and strawberry jam ♪
♪ And they don't lose any sleep at night ♪
♪ Cause Earl had to die ♪
♪ Na na na na na ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Earl ♪
♪ We need a break ♪
♪ Let's go out to the lake ♪
♪ Earl ♪
♪ We'll pack a lunch ♪
♪ Na na na na na ♪
♪ Stuff you in the trunk ♪
♪ Earl ♪
♪ Well is that alright? ♪
♪ Na na na na na ♪
♪ Good! Let's go for a ride ♪
♪ Earl ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Na na na na na ♪
♪ Oh hey hey hey! ♪
♪ Well, hey hey hey! ♪
♪ Na na na na na ♪